Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Boxed Games, 1972-2007 and undated, (76 boxes)
  - General Games
    - Prestags Master-Pack: Five Complete Simulation Games from the Pre-Seventeeth Century Tactical Game System: Chariot: Tactical Warefare in the "Biblical" Age, 3000-500BC; Spartan: Tactical Warfare in the Hellenistic Age, 500-100BC; Legion: Tactical Warfare in the Roman Age, 100BC-700AD; Viking: Tactical Warfare in the Dark Ages, 700-1300; Yeoman: Tactical Warfare in the Renaissance Age, 1250-1550. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1976., D02482595Z (Box BG 34)
    - Prime Directive: The Star Fleet Universe Role-Playing Game. Published by Task Force Games, 1993., D02340851N (Box BG 54)
    - Privateers and Gentlemen: Role Playing Adventure in the Age of Fighting Sailing. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1984., D02482587- (Box BG 26)
    - PSI World: Role Playing Game of Psionic Powers. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1984., D02482584X (Box BG 23)
    - Quest: A Game of the Knights of the Round Table. Published by Gametime Games, 1978., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - Quirks: the game of un-natural selection!. Published by EON Products, Inc., 1980., D02340842N (Box BG 46)
    - Ram Speed. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340855R (Box BG 58)
    - Rommel's Panzers. Published by Metagaming, undated., D02340855R (Box BG 58)
    - Runes: a different kind of word game. Published by EON Products, Inc., 1981., D02340841M (Box BG 45)
    - Sea-Steeds and Wave Riders by Dave Sering, no. 66. Published by Judges Guild, 1978., D02482571T (Box BG 10)
    - Security Station: A high technology labyrinth. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Shadowrun: Downtown Militarized Zone. Published by FASA Corporation, 1991., D02340851N (Box BG 54)
    - Shatterzone. Published by West End Games, Inc., 1983., D02482585Y (Box BG 24)
    - Skull & Crossbones: Role Play on the Spanish Main. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1980., D02482587- (Box BG 26)
    - Snapshot: Close Combat Aboard Starships in the Far Future. Published by Game Designers' Workshop, 1979., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - Snit's Revenge. Published by TSR, Inc., 1978., D02340846R (Box BG 50)
    - Sorcerer: The Game of Magical Conflict. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1975., D02340833N (Box BG 37)
    - Source of the Nile: African Exploration in the 19th Century. Published by Discovery Games, 1978., D02340846R (Box BG 50)
    - Space Opera. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1980., D02340836Q (Box BG 40)
    - Space Opera. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1981., D02340836Q (Box BG 40)
    - Spellmaker: A Game of Mysticism and Magic. Published by Gametime Games, 1978., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - Spies! The multiplayer game of international intrigue. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1981., D02340930L (Box BG 64)
    - Stalin's Tanks: Armor battles on the Russian front. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Star Ace: Adventures in Space. Published by Pacesetter, 1984., D02482585Y (Box BG 24)
    - Star First: The Terran Space Fleet Faces a Killer Asteroid. Published by Steve Jackson Games, 1991., D02340848T (Box BG 51)
    - Star Fleet Battle. Published by Task Force Games, 1979., D02482584X (Box BG 23)
    - Star Force Trilogy: Star Force: Interstellar Conflict in the 25th Century; Outreach: The Conquest of the Galaxy, 3000AD; Star Soldier: Tactical Warfare in the 25th Century. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1977., D02482595Z (Box BG 34)
    - Star Frontiers. Published by TSR, Inc., 1980., D02482578- (Box BG 17)
    - Star Frontiers: Knight Hawks. Published by TSR, Inc., 1983., D02482578- (Box BG 17)
    - Star Patrol. Published by Gamescience, 1981., D02482578- (Box BG 17)
    - Star Smuggler. Published by Heritage USA, 1982., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Star Traders: Race across the galaxy…for the treasures of a hundred worlds. Published by Steve Jackson Games, 1987., D02340848T (Box BG 51)
    - Star Viking: A Game of Interstellar Raiding and Plunder. Published by Heritage USA, 1981., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Starfleet Voyages. Published by Terra Games, 1982., D02482579. (Box BG 18)
    - Starleader Assault: A Futuristic Man-To-Man Combat Game. Published by Metagaming, 1982., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Stellar Conquest: The Classic Game of Societies in Conflict. Published by Metagaming, 1979., D02340849U (Box BG 52)
    - Super Squandron: The Complete Superhero Role-Playing Game System. Published by Adventure Simulations, 1983., D02482586Z (Box BG 25)
    - Superstar: Pro Wrestling Game. Published by Super Star Game Co., Inc., 1984., D02340841M (Box BG 45)
    - Superworld: The Super Powered Role Playing Game. Published by Chaosium Inc., 1983., D02340835P (Box BG 39)
    - Swashbuckler: A game of Swordplay and Derring-do. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1980., D02340854Q (Box BG 57)
    - Swordbearer. Published by Heritage USA, 1982., D02482575X (Box BG 14)
    - Swords and Sorcery: Quest and Conquest in the Age of Magic. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1978., D02340930L (Box BG 64)
    - Tales of the Arabian Nights. Published by West End Games, Inc., 1985., D02482583W (Box BG 22)
    - The Air-Eaters Strike Back!. Published by Metagaming, 1981., D02340855R (Box BG 58)
    - The Awful Green Things From Outer Space. Published by TSR, Inc., 1980., D02340846R (Box BG 50)
    - The Barbarians: Games of the Fall of Rome and the Mongol Invasion of Europe. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1981., D02340854Q (Box BG 57)
    - The Beast Lord: A game of Wizardry and Warfare. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1979., D02482592W (Box BG 31)
    - The Brotherhood: The game of Organized Crime. Published by Game Designers' Workshop, 1983., D02340849U (Box BG 52)
    - The French Foreign Legion. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1982., D02340854Q (Box BG 57)
    - The Fury of the Norsemen: A Rollicking Game of Plunder and Pillage. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - The Great Maze: Dead Lands. Published by Pinnacle Entertainment Group, Inc., 1997., D02340836Q (Box BG 40)
    - The Last Starfighter: Duel in Space. Published by FASA Corporation (Universal Lorimar Joint Venture), 1984., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - The Last Starfighter: Tunnel Chase. Published by FASA Corporation (Universal Lorimar Joint Venture), 1984., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - The Lords of Underearth. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - The Plot to Assassinate Hitler, 1940-1945. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1976., D02340930L (Box BG 64)
    - The Punic Wars: Rome vs. Carthage, 264-146 B.C.. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1975., D02340835P (Box BG 39)
    - The Roaring 20's: A Game of Gangsters. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1981., D02340854Q (Box BG 57)
    - The Sorcerer's Cave. Published by Ariel, 1978., D02340854Q (Box BG 57)
    - The Sword and the Stars. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1981., D02340848T (Box BG 51)
    - The Thieves' World: Complete Sanctuary Adventure Pack. Published by Chaosium Inc., 1981., D02340873R (Box BG 62)
    - The Thieves' World: Sanctuary. Published by Mayfair Games, undated., D04564071R (Box BG 75)
    - The Trojan War: The Game of Gods and Heroes. Published by Metagaming, 1981., D02340855R (Box BG 58)
    - The Valley of the Pharaoh: Role Playing Adventure in Ancient Egypt. Published by Palladium Books, 1983., D02340836Q (Box BG 40)
    - The War of the Worlds. Published by Task Force Games, 1980., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - The Warlord Game. Published by Robert Williams Games, 1976., D02482596- (Box BG 35)
    - The World of Indiana Jones. Published by West End Games, Inc., 1994., D037748691 (Box BG 1)
    - Thieves Guild. Published by Gamelords, 1984., D02340847S (Box BG 73)
    - Time & Time Again: The Time Travel Role Playing Game. Published by Timeline Ltd., 1984., D02482583W (Box BG 22)
    - Time Master: Adventures in the 4th Dimension. Published by Pacesetter, 1984., D02482585Y (Box BG 24)
    - Time Tripper. Published by Simulations Publications, Inc., 1980., D02340837R (Box BG 41)
    - Time War. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1979., D02482590U (Box BG 29)
    - Timeship: A role playing game of time travel and adventure. Published by Yaquinto Publications, 1983., D02482583W (Box BG 22)
    - Trailblazer. Published by Metagaming, 1981., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - Treasure of the Silver Dragon. Published by Metagaming, 1980., D02340903L (Box BG 63)
    - Treasure of Unicorn Gold. Published by Metagaming, 1981., D02340853P (Box BG 56)
    - Triplanetary: Space Combat in the Solar System 2001. Published by Game Designers' Workshop, 1981., D02340833N (Box BG 37)
    - Twilight: 2000. Published by Game Designers' Workshop, 1984., D02340837R (Box BG 41)
    - Valley of the Four Winds: An Epic Game of Swords and Sorcery. Published by Games Workshop Ltd, 1980., D02340838S (Box BG 42)
    - Villians and Vigilantes. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1982., D02482586Z (Box BG 25)
    - Wabbit Wampage. Published by Pacesetter, 1985., D02482580T (Box BG 19)
    - Warlocks & Warriors: Introductory Level. Published by TSR, Inc., 1977., D02340842N (Box BG 46)
    - Wild West: A Role Playing Game Set in the Old West. Published by Fantasy Games Unlimited, 1981., D02482581U (Box BG 20)
    - Witch Hunt: Role Playing: Salem 1692. Published by Statcom Simulations Inc., 1983., D02482583W (Box BG 22)
    - Worlds of Wonder. Published by Chaosium Inc., 1982., D02340835P (Box BG 39)
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2009 and undated, (2399 volumes)
  The Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes series includes books designed to accompany or enable role-playing in a variety of worlds. A volume typically includes campaign settings, character guides, game system rules, or reference tools for players. Worlds represented in this series include Dungeons and Dragons, Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, Birthright, Cyberpunk, Call of Cthulhu, Dragon Lance, Earthdawn, Forgotten Realms, Middle Earth, Ravenloft, Spell Jammer, and many more.
  Most volumes are individually numbered and barcoded, unless they included extra components that required them to be housed in a box. There are 6 boxes of volumes (M1-M6) included in this series. All volumes (regardless of volume or box number) have been arranged by alphabetically by game world, then chronologically by date. General volumes that have no identifiable "world" are listed at the end in alphabetical order. A spreadsheet is available for researchers who are interested in sorting the games in a different way.
  - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons
    - Monster Manual: An Illustrated Compendium of Monsters. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1977., D03805784Z (Box BG 39, Volume 560)
    - Descent into the Depths of the Earth. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382952X (Box BG 39, Volume 1253)
    - Hall of the Fire Giant King. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382953Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1254)
    - Players Handbook. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D03574359- (Box BG 39, Volume 568)
    - Player's Handbook. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04403837T (Box BG 39, Volume 1758)
    - Shrine of the Kuo-Toa. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382951W (Box BG 39, Volume 1252)
    - Steading of the Hill Giant Chief. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382955- (Box BG 39, Volume 1256)
    - The Glacial Rift of the Frost Giant Jarl. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382954Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1255)
    - Tomb of Horrors. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382972Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1275)
    - Vault of the Drow. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1978., D04382950V (Box BG 39, Volume 1251)
    - Character Codex. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403979- (Box BG 39, Volume 1771)
    - Dark Tower: Fantasy Game Aid. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403758V (Box BG 39, Volume 1566)
    - Dungeon Masters Guide. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D03574354V (Box BG 39, Volume 573)
    - Dungeon Masters Guide. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04403835R (Box BG 39, Volume 1757)
    - Dungeon Masters Screen. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04403814O (Box BG 39, Volume 1640)
    - Permenant Character and Adventure Records. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04403940O (Box BG 39, Volume 1760)
    - Player Character Record Sheets. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04403942Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1762)
    - Temple of Ra Accursed by Set. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403684T (Box BG 39, Volume 1508)
    - The Maltese Clue. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403683S (Box BG 39, Volume 1507)
    - The Treasure Vaults of Lindoran. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1979., D04403663Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1488)
    - The Village of Hommlet. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04382944Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1245)
    - White Plume Mountain. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1979., D04382971Y (Box BG 39, Volume 1274)
    - Danger at Dunwater. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382974. (Box BG 39, Volume 1277)
    - Deities and Demigods. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D03574336V (Box BG 39, Volume 640)
    - Escape from Astigar's Lair. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1980., D04403685U (Box BG 39, Volume 1509)
    - Expedition to the Barrier Peaks. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382970X (Box BG 39, Volume 1273)
    - Fiend Folio: Tome of Creatures Malevolent and Benign. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D03574338X (Box BG 39, Volume 639)
    - In the Dungeons of the Slave Lords. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382947. (Box BG 39, Volume 1249)
    - Inferno. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1980., D04403682R (Box BG 39, Volume 1506)
    - Portals of Torsh. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1980., D04403760O (Box BG 39, Volume 1568)
    - Queen of the Demonweb Pits. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382975 (Box BG 39, Volume 1278)
    - Slave Pits of the Undercity. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382956. (Box BG 39, Volume 1257)
    - The Ghost Tower of Inverness. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1980., D04383067V (Box BG 39, Volume 1410)
    - The Hidden Shrine of Tamoachan. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1980., D04382942W (Box BG 39, Volume 1243)
    - Assault on the Aerie of the Slave Lords. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04382959/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1259)
    - Dragon's Hall. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403659V (Box BG 39, Volume 1484)
    - Dwellers of the Forbidden City. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04382948 (Box BG 39, Volume 1250)
    - House on Hangman's Hill. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403658U (Box BG 39, Volume 1483)
    - Lara's Tower. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403669W (Box BG 39, Volume 1494)
    - Non-Player Character Records. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04403943R (Box BG 39, Volume 1763)
    - Player Character Record Sheets. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04403941P (Box BG 39, Volume 1761)
    - Portals of Irontooth. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04382921T (Box BG 39, Volume 1534)
    - Portals of Twilight. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403699Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1535)
    - Secret of the Slavers Stockade. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04382957 (Box BG 39, Volume 1258)
    - The Book of Ruins. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403759W (Box BG 39, Volume 1567)
    - The Illhiedrin Book. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403735Q (Box BG 39, Volume 1545)
    - The Secret of Bone Hill. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04382940U (Box BG 39, Volume 1241)
    - The Sinister Secret of Saltmarsh. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1981., D04382978+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1280)
    - Tower of Jourdar. Published by Littleton, CO: Dimension Six, Inc., 1981., D04403804N (Box BG 39, Volume 1629)
    - Trial by Fire. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403729T (Box BG 39, Volume 1539)
    - Zienteck. Published by Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc., 1981., D04403676U (Box BG 39, Volume 1499)
    - Against the Cult of the Reptile God. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382943X (Box BG 39, Volume 1244)
    - Dark Folk: Trolls, Orcs, Goblins, Kobolds, Gnolls. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1982., D04403723N (Box BG 39, Volume 1624)
    - Dwarves. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1982., D04403724O (Box BG 39, Volume 1625)
    - Pharaoh. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1982., D04382212M (Box BG 39, Volume 485)
    - The Egg of the Phoenix. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382279Z (Box BG 39, Volume 611)
    - The Forgotten Temple of Tharizdun. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382968/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1271)
    - The Investigation of Hydell. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382280R (Box BG 39, Volume 612)
    - The Lost Caverns of Tsojcanth. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382969+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1272)
    - To the Aid of Falx. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1982., D04382281S (Box BG 39, Volume 613)
    - Tomb of the Lizard King. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1982., D04382211L (Box BG 39, Volume 486)
    - Beyond the Crystal Cave. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382941V (Box BG 39, Volume 1242)
    - Black Opal Eye. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382263S (Box BG 39, Volume 589)
    - Doc's Island. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382278Y (Box BG 39, Volume 610)
    - Dragons of Weng T'Sen. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1983., D04382992. (Box BG 39, Volume 1304)
    - Dungeonland. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382946- (Box BG 39, Volume 1247)
    - Evil Ruins. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1983., D04382991- (Box BG 39, Volume 1303)
    - Lost Tomb of Martek. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382215P (Box BG 39, Volume 483)
    - Monster Manual II. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D03574367Z (Box BG 39, Volume 561)
    - Oasis of the White Palm. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382213N (Box BG 39, Volume 484)
    - Rahasia. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382264T (Box BG 39, Volume 590)
    - Shipwrecker. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1983., D043829890 (Box BG 39, Volume 1300)
    - The Assassin's Knot. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382939 (Box BG 39, Volume 1240)
    - The Elixir of Life. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382261Q (Box BG 39, Volume 587)
    - The Final Enemy. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382973- (Box BG 39, Volume 1276)
    - The Forgotten King. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382262R (Box BG 39, Volume 588)
    - The Keep. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1983., D04382996+ (Box BG 39, Volume 1308)
    - The Land Beyond the Magic Mirror. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1983., D04382945Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1246)
    - The Sentinel. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1983., D04382960W (Box BG 39, Volume 1260)
    - All That Glitters. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382219T (Box BG 39, Volume 488)
    - Conan: Against Darkness!. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382258W (Box BG 39, Volume 584)
    - Conan: Unchained!. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382259X (Box BG 39, Volume 585)
    - Eye of the Serpent. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382218S (Box BG 39, Volume 489)
    - Fantastic Treasures. Published by Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1984., D04403836S (Box BG 39, Volume 1669)
    - Midnight on Dagger Alley. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382772X (Box BG 39, Volume 1135)
    - Monsters of Myth and Legend. Published by Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, 1984., D04403725P (Box BG 39, Volume 1641)
    - Shadows of Evil. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1984., D04382724U (Box BG 39, Volume 1301)
    - Swordthrust. Published by Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1984., D04382986/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1294)
    - The Forest Oracle. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382257V (Box BG 39, Volume 583)
    - The Gauntlet. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382961X (Box BG 39, Volume 1261)
    - The Lost Island of Castanamir. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382779/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1134)
    - Throne of Evil. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1984., D04382990Z (Box BG 39, Volume 1302)
    - To Find a King. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382282T (Box BG 39, Volume 614)
    - When a Star Falls. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1984., D04382217R (Box BG 39, Volume 490)
    - Baltron's Beacon. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382214O (Box BG 39, Volume 482)
    - Dark Clouds Gather. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04382220L (Box BG 39, Volume 487)
    - Dungeon Master's Screen. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04403813N (Box BG 39, Volume 1639)
    - Fantastic Treasures II. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1985., D04403823O (Box BG 39, Volume 1644)
    - Lich Lords. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1985., D04382995/ (Box BG 39, Volume 1307)
    - Oriental Adventures. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D03574360S (Box BG 39, Volume 569)
    - The Temple of Elemental Evil. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D04405671R (Box BG 39, Volume 1269)
    - Unearthed Arcana. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1985., D03574366Y (Box BG 39, Volume 562)
    - Day of Al'Akbar. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382207Q (Box BG 39, Volume 479)
    - Destiny of Kings. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382216Q (Box BG 39, Volume 491)
    - Dragons. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1986., D04382722S (Box BG 39, Volume 1309)
    - Dungeoneer's Survival Guide. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D03574358Z (Box BG 39, Volume 570)
    - Pinnacle. Published by Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc., 1986., D04382988% (Box BG 39, Volume 1299)
    - Player Character Record Sheets. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc., 1986., D04403939W (Box BG 39, Volume 1759)
    - Queen of the Spicers. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382734V (Box BG 39, Volume 1263)
    - Ravager of Time. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382205O (Box BG 39, Volume 481)
    - Red Sonja Unconquered. Published by Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc., 1986., D04382260P (Box BG 39, Volume 586)